Hi, mommy. Thanks for bringing
us joy and happiness. Just so
you know, I'll bring that to
you too. Thank you for loving
us and taking care of us and
making sure we get what we need
and why and most of all, thank
you for giving us a family.
Here, mommy. Thanks for always
being there for us. I hope you
know that we'll always be there
for you too. Happy Mother's
Day. Whoo. Dream Lucy Legacy.
Orange and Lotto. Give you.
Happy Mother's Day. We love
you, mommy. We love you. Stop.
I cannot. Wait, have a good
one. Thank you for cleaning up
my messes. Why are you
recording for buying us all
that gluten-free sweet? Again,
thanks for taking us around the
world.
Oh lord return me to
I love that you love us. I love
that you always make us feel
safe. I wish I could give you
the power to get whatever you
want. Happy Mother's Day. I
love you. By the power, I will
give you the whole world. I
hope this video makes your day.
Happy Mother's Day. We love
you. We love you.
You next to me when we see
Happy Mother's Day.
Can we get gelato now? Just
kidding, mommy. We love you. We
love you. We love you. But
seriously, I do want gelato.
And we mean it. What? Did you
want gelato or did you love
her? No. Obi poopy Kenobi.
Obi. Obi poopy smelling Obi.
Obi poopy Kenobi. Happy
Mother's Day mommy. We love
you. Happy Mother's Day. Me and
little booger butt. Oh.
You're just being silly.